<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Darrell Tang</title><link>https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Darrell Tang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:15:09 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create Your Own Personal Site with Github Pages &amp; Hugo</title><link>https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/workshops/github-pages-site/github-pages-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:15:09 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/workshops/github-pages-site/github-pages-site/</guid><description>Why are we doing this? Standing out in the job market nowadays requires higher visibility and Github offers free personal websites for your user profile and any Github repos with Github Pages.
A personal website can offer:
A useful tool for networking and building professional connections. By having a personal website, you can make it easier for others to find and contact you, and you can use it as a platform to promote your professional skills and experiences.</description></item><item><title>Prework</title><link>https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/workshops/github-pages-site/prework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:15:09 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/workshops/github-pages-site/prework/</guid><description> Create a Github account Create and Upload an SSH Key to Github Install git Install hugo (Optional) Install VS Code editor</description></item><item><title>Create and Upload an SSH Key to Github</title><link>https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/github-ssh/create-and-upload-ssh-key-to-github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 19:56:15 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://darrelltang.github.io/posts/github-ssh/create-and-upload-ssh-key-to-github/</guid><description>To generate an SSH key and upload it to GitHub, follow these steps:
Open a terminal on your computer and run the following command: ssh-keygen -t ed25519 -b 512 When prompted, enter a file in which to save the key. You can press Enter to accept the default file location. Next, you will be asked to enter a passphrase for the key. This is an optional security measure that adds an extra layer of protection to your key.</description></item></channel></rss>